<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>kapow.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kapow Punch Clock</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kapow – evidence odpracovaného času</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Kapow stopur</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kapow Zeiterfassung</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Kapow Punch Clock</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Reloj de control Kapow</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Kapow - sinu tööaja arvestus</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Pointeuse Kapow</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kapow, il timbra cartellino</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Kapow kontrolinis laikrodis</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kapow-prikklok</name>
  <name xml:lang="no">Kapow Stemplingsur</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Rejestracja czasu pracy Kapow</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kapow Punch Clock</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Relógio de ponto Kapow</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Kapow Punch Clock</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Kapow Punch Clock</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kapow Stämpelklocka</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Kapow Kokteyl Saat</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kapow Punch Clock</name>
  <summary>Keep track of time spent on projects</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Udržujte si přehled o času stráveném nad projekty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Hold styr på, hvor meget tid der bruges på projekter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Verfolgen Sie Ihre Arbeitszeiten an Projekten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Παρακολουθήστε το χρόνο που δαπανάτε σε έργα</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Pea arvet erinevatele projektidele kulutatud aja üle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Realice un seguimiento del tiempo que invierte en proyectos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Conservez une trace du temps passé sur vos projets</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Tieni traccia del tempo speso nel progetto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Sekite projektams išleistą laiką</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Houd de tijd bij die u spendeert aan projecten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="no">Ha kontroll over tidsforbruk på prosjekter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Śledź twój czas poświęcony na projekty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Controle o tempo gasto em projectos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Mantenha o registro do tempo gasto em projetos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Ţineţi evidenţa timpului petrecut pe proiecte</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Следите за временем, затраченным на проекты</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Håll koll på tiden som du spenderar på projekt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Projeler için harcanan zamanı takip edin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Слідкуйте за часом, витраченим на проекти </summary>

  <description>
    <p>Kapow is a punch clock program designed to easily keep track of your hours, whether you're working on one project or many. Simply clock in and out with the Start/Stop button. If you make a mistake in your hours, you can go back and edit any of the entries by double-clicking on the session in question. Kapow also allows you to easily keep track of the hours since you last billed a client, by providing a helpful "Billed" check box--the totals will reflect your work after the last billed session.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Kapow je aplikace pro evidenci odpracovaného času navržená pro snadné udržování si přehledu o hodinách, ať už strávených nad jedním nebo více projekty. Jednoduše si kliknutím na příslušné tlačítko zaznamenejte zahájení a přerušení/skončení práce. Pokud se zmýlíte, můžete se vrátit a kterýkoli ze záznamů upravit dvojklikem na příslušné sezení. Kapow také umožňuje snadné udržování přehledu o hodinách, odpracovaných od minulého zúčtování s klientem a to praktickou zaškrtávací kolonkou „Účtováno“. Součty budou odpovídat vaší práci od posledního zúčtovaného sezení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Kapow er et tidstagningsprogram beregnet til at holde styr på dine timer, om du så arbejder på et enkelt projekt eller mange. Check ind og ud med start/stop-knappen. Laver du en fejl i din registrering, kan du gå tilbage og redigere den ved at dobbeltklikke på den. Kapow gør det også nemt at holde styr på, hvor mange timer der er kommet til siden du sidst fakturerede en kunde med en praktisk afkrydsningsboks med "faktureret" - så vil den totale tid afspejle den tid, der er gået siden den seneste faktura er udarbejdet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Kapow ist eine Zeiterfassungssoftware und wurde entwickelt, um leichter den Überblick über Ihre Stunden, die Sie an einem Projekt arbeiten zu behalten. Einfach die Stempeluhr beginnen oder stoppen mit der Start/Stop-Taste. Wenn Sie einen Fehler in der Stunde machen, können Sie zurückgehen und bearbeiten einen der Einträge mit einem Doppelklick auf die Sitzung. Mit Kapow können Sie auch leicht den Überblick über die Stunden seit der letzten Rechnung eines Kunden durch die Bereitstellung eines hilfreichen "Billed" aktivieren - die Summe wird Ihre Arbeit nach der letzten Rechnung der Sitzung an berechnen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Kapow είναι ένα πρόγραμμα χρονομέτρου εργασίας, σχεδιασμένο για εύκολη παρακολούθηση των ωρών, όποτε εργάζεστε σε ένα ή περισσότερα έργα. Απλός έλεγχος του ρολογιού με το πάτημα ενός κουμπιού Έναρξης/Διακοπής. Εάν κάνετε κάποιο λάθος κατά τις ώρες σας, μπορείτε να επιστρέψετε πίσω και να επεξεργαστείτε οποιαδήποτε από τις καταγραφές, κάνοντας διπλό κλικ στη σχετική σύνοδο. Το Kapow σας δίνει επίσης τη δυνατότητα να παρακολουθείτε εύκολα τις ώρες από την τελευταία σας χρέωση σε έναν πελάτη, παρέχοντας ένα χρήσιμο πλαίσιο ελέγχου "Χρέωσης", παρουσιάζοντας έτσι τα συνολικά ποσά που αντιστοιχούν στην εργασίας σας μετά την τελευταία χρέωση.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Kapow on tööaja arvestuse programm, mis on mõeldud väga lihtsaks töötundide arvestamiseks ühe või enama projekti kontekstis. Lihtsalt käivita ja peata taimer nii, nagu vaja on. Kui tekkis mõni viga, siis klõpsates antud sessiooni salvestatud andmetele saad neid kergesti muuta. Lisaks on sul mugav pidada arvet kliendile esitatud arvete üle - andmetes on vastav märkekast ning siis kõik summad kajastavad eelmisest arvest kulunud aega.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Kapow est une pointeuse horaire conçue pour conserver facilement une trace de votre temps passé à travailler sur un ou sur plusieurs projets. Pointez et dépointez simplement à l'aide du bouton Démarrer/Arrêter. Si vous vous êtes trompé(e) dans vos heures, vous pouvez revenir dessus et éditer l'une des entrées en double-cliquant sur la session en question. Kapow vous permet aussi de conserver une trace des heures que vous devrez au final facturer au client, en proposant une case « Facturé » bien pratique. Les totaux refléteront votre travail après la dernière session facturée. </p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Kapow è un programma "timbra cartellino",  dal design semplice,  creata per aiutarti a tener traccia delle ore di lavoro su uno o molti progetti. E' un semplice orologio di inizio e fine grazie ad un pulsante di Start e Stop. Se commetti un errore quando registri le tue ore, puoi tranquillamente editare i dati cliccando due volte il nome della sessione. Kapow ti aiuta a tenera traccia delle ore fatturate ad un cliente, grazie all'utilissima check box "Fatturato" che ti mostra il tuo ammontare, partendo dall'ultima fatturazione</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Kapow yra kontrolinio laikrodžio programa, skirta sekti valandas, nesvarbu, ar dirbama su vienu, ar su daugeliu projektų. Paprastai valdykite laiką mygtuku Pradėti/Stabdyti. Jei savo valandose suklydote, galite grįžti ir, spustelėję du kartus, keisti įrašus. Taip pat Kapow, suteikdama naudingą žymimąjį langelį "Apmokestinta", leidžia lengvai sekti valandas nuo to laiko, kuomet paskutinį kartą apmokestinote savo klientą--sumos atspindės jūsų darbą nuo paskutinės apmokestintos sesijos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kapow is een prikklokprogramma, ontworpen om gemakkelijk uw uren bij te kunnen houden, of u nu werkt aan één of aan meerdere projecten. Klok in en uit met de Start/Stop-knop. Als u een fout maakt, dan kunt u teruggaan en elke invoer bewerken door te dubbelklikken op de bijbehorende sessie. Kapow laat u tevens gemakkelijk bijhouden wanneer u voor het laatst een cliënt hebt gefactureerd middels het selectievakje ‘Gefactureerd’. Het totaal geeft uw werkuren aan sinds de laatst gefactureerde sessie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="no">Kapow er et elektronisk stemplingsur som holder kontroll på ditt tidsforbruk, enten du jobber på ett eller flere prosjekt. Du stempler bare inn og ut med Start/Stopp knappen. Gjør du en feil, kan du enkelt rette denne ved å dobbeltklikke på oppføringen du vil endre. Kapow gir deg oversikt på tidsforbruk siden siste faktura, ved en enkel avkrysning for fakturert tid, - totalen vil gjenspeile tidsforbruk siden forrige faktura.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kapow to program rejestracji czasu pracy przeznaczony do łatwego śledzenia swoich godzin, gdy pracujesz nad jednym lub wielu projektach. Po prostu zastartuj/zatrzymaj zegar przyciskiem Start/Stop. Jeśli popełnisz błąd w zapisie swoich godzin, możesz cofnąć i zmienić jedną z pozycji, klikając dwukrotnie na sesję w pytaniu. Kapow pozwala także łatwo śledzić godziny od ostatniego rozliczania z klientem, poprzez dostarczenie pola pomocniczego "rozliczone" wyboru--sumy będą rozliczane twoją pracę po ostatniej sesji.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Kapow é um programa com as funcionalidades de um relógio de ponto concebido para ser fácil de rastrear as horas, quer esteja a trabalhar num projecto ou vários. Simplesmente registe as "entradas" e "saídas" com o botão Iniciar/Parar. Se cometer um erro nas horas, pode voltar atrás e editar qualquer uma das entradas com um clique duplo na sessão em questão. O Kapow também permite rastrear facilmente as horas utilizadas após as últimas facturadas a um cliente, através da opção "Facturado" - os totais irão refletir as horas utilizadas após a última sessão faċturada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Kapow este un program de ceas stimul conceput pentru a ţine evidenţa orelor dvs., indiferent dacă lucraţi pe un proiect sau mai multe. Pur şi simplu cronometraţi cu butonul Start/Stop. Dacă faceţi o greşeală în orele dvs., vă puteţi întoarce şi edita oricare dintre intrări dînd dublu-clic pe sesiunea în cauză. Kapow, de asemenea, vă permite să păstraţi cu uşurinţă evidenţa orelor de cînd aţi facturat în trecut un client, bifînd căsuţa ajutătoare "Taxat" - totalurile vor reflecta munca, după ultima sesiune facturată.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Kapow - это програма по учёту времени разработанная для простого отслеживания Ваших часов, как-бы Вы не работали над одним или несколькими проектами. Просто используйте часы с помощью кнопок Старт/Стоп. Если Вы допустите ошибку в Ваших замерах времени, Вы можете вернуться назад и изменить любую запись с помощью двойного нажатия на рассматриваемую сессию. Kapow также может легко отслеживать время с момента последнего выставления счёта клиенту, предоставляя полезный флажок «Счета»--итоговые суммы будут отражать Вашу работу после последнего выставленного счёта.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kapow är ett stämpelklocksprogram som är enkelt utformat för att hålla koll på dina timmar, oavsett om du arbetar på ett eller flera projekt. Stämpla helt enkelt in och ut med Start/Stopp-knappen. Om du gör ett misstag i dina timmar, kan du gå tillbaka och redigera någon av posterna genom att dubbelklicka på den aktuella sessionen. Kapow låter dig även enkelt hålla koll på timmarna sedan du senast fakturerade en kund, genom att tillhandahålla en användbar "Fakturerat"-kryssruta. Summan kommer att återspegla ditt arbete efter den senast fakturerade sessionen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kapow — це програма, яка дозволяє легко відстежувати ваші години роботи, незалежно від того, чи працюєте ви над одним проектом чи кількома. Просто ввімкніть і вийміть годинник за допомогою кнопки Пуск/Стоп. Якщо ви зробили помилку в годиннику, ви можете повернутися назад і відредагувати будь-який із записів, двічі клацнувши відповідний сеанс. Kapow також дозволяє легко відстежувати години з моменту останнього виставлення рахунку клієнту, встановлюючи корисний прапорець «Оплачено» — підсумки відображатимуть вашу роботу після останнього сеансу, що виставлявся.</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gottcode.org/kapow/screenshots/kapow.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gottcode.org/kapow/screenshots/report1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gottcode.org/kapow/screenshots/report2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://gottcode.org/kapow/screenshots/report3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://gottcode.org/kapow/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gottcode.org/kapow/bugs/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://gottcode.org/tip/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.transifex.com/gottcode/kapow/</url>

  <developer id="org.gottcode">
    <name translatable="no">Graeme Gott</name>
  </developer>
  <update_contact>graeme@gottcode.org</update_contact>

  <translation type="qt">kapow</translation>

  <provides>
    <binary>kapow</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">kapow.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="stock">kapow</icon>

  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>Calendar</category>
  </categories>

  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.6.2" date="2024-01-16">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Did not quit when close-to-tray was enabled</li>
          <li>FIXED: System tray icon did not work in Windows</li>
          <li>Only allow a single instance to run</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Spanish, Turkish</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.6.1" date="2023-01-10">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow higher hourly rate</li>
          <li>Improved Linux deployment</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Italian, Portuguese</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.6.0" date="2022-05-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added optional closing to tray</li>
          <li>Added removing last report</li>
          <li>Always allow creating report if there are unbilled sessions</li>
          <li>Always use exact value for totals in reports</li>
          <li>Only save when timers are active</li>
          <li>Prevent adding or editing session after start of running timer</li>
          <li>Prevent starting or ending timer inside of existing session</li>
          <li>Refactored code</li>
          <li>Switched to Qt 6</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Czech, Dutch, French, Lithuanian, Romanian, Ukrainian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.10" date="2020-04-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Did not load locales with underscores</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Italian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.9" date="2019-08-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Window icon didn't work in Wayland</li>
          <li>Improved loading locales</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Czech, French</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.8" date="2018-07-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Automatic high DPI support</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.7" date="2018-06-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Crash when adding projects</li>
          <li>FIXED: Crash when removing projects with multiple subprojects</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.6" date="2018-05-29">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Extra warnings only shown in debug build</li>
          <li>Improved Linux deployment</li>
          <li>Improved macOS deployment</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Danish, Portuguese</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
